Guide to the Jewish Community Council of Greater Washington records, 1937-1988 MS2012
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Committees, task torces, and working groups, 1941-1983; MS2012 Series 2; 22.5 Linear feet
  - Soviet Jewry: Beryozka Dance Company Demonstration, 1972 November 25-26 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Soviet Jewry: Women's Plea for Soviet Jewry, 1972 December 11 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Soviet Jewry: Refuseniks and Prisoners of Conscience, 1972 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Soviet Jewry: Adopt a Prisoner Project, 1972 (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Soviet Jewry: National Conference on Soviet Jewry, 1972 (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Soviet Jewry: Soviet Jewry Newsletters - JCCGW "Undercover,", 1972 (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - Soviet Jewry: American Jewish conference on Soviet Jewry, 1972 (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - Soviet Jewry: Washington Committee for Soviet Jewry, 1972 (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - Soviet Jewry: Testimony of Avraham Shifrin before Senate Subcommittee, 1973 February 01 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Soviet Jewry: Jurists Appeal for Amnesty for Imprisoned Soviet Jews, 1973 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Soviet Jewry: National Association of Manufactures Conference on Soviet Trade, Washington, D.C., 1973 February 27 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Soviet Jewry: Jackson/Mills-Vanik Legislation on East-West Trade and Freedom of Emigration, 1973 March-December (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Soviet Jewry: Jackson/Mills-Vanik Legislation on East-West Trade and Freedom of Emigration, 1973 March-December (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Soviet Jewry: National Freedom Assembly for Soviet Jewry, 1973 June 17 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Soviet Jewry: National Freedom Assembly for Soviet Jewry, 1973 June 17 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Soviet Jewry: National Freedom Assembly for Soviet Jewry, 1973 June 17 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Soviet Jewry: Anti-Semitic Attacks of World University Games - Moscow, 1973 August 19 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Soviet Jewry: New Years Greeting Card Program to Soviet Jews and Synagogues, 1973 August-September (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Soviet Jewry: Community Meeting for Leonid Tarassuk, 1973 September 10 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Soviet Jewry: Simhat Torah Demonstration for Soviet Jewry, 1973 October 14 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Soviet Jewry: Women's Plea for Soviet Jewry, 1973 December 10 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Soviet Jewry: Women's Plea for Soviet Jewry, 1973 December 10 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Soviet Jewry Vigil, 1973 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Soviet Jewry: Refusniks and Prisoners of Conscience, 1973 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Soviet Jewry: Adopt a Prisoner Project, 1973 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Soviet Jewry: National Conference on Soviet Jewry, 1973 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Soviet Jewry: National Conference on Soviet Jewry News Release, 1973 (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Soviet Jewry Newsletter - "Backgrounder,", 1973 (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - Soviet Jewry: Report on Jewish Scientists Seeking to Emigrate, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Soviet Jewry: Report on Soviet Jewish Immigrants in Washington, 1974 January-April (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Soviet Jewry: Meeting with Sima Kominsky (wife of Lassal Kominsky), 1974 January 29 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Soviet Jewry: Soviet Trade Delegation, 1974 February 26 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Soviet Jewry: Moscow Hunger Strike, 1974 February (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Soviet Jewry: Demonstration for Valery and Galina Panov, 1974 March 12 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Soviet Jewry: Matzah Delivery to Soviet Embassy/Matzah of Hope, 1974 April (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Soviet Jewry: Jackson Legislation on East-West Trade and Freedom of Emigration, 1974 June-December (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Soviet Jewry: Tribute to Soviet Jewish Art and Culture, 1974 June 23 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Soviet Jewry: Tribute to Soviet Jewish Art and Culture, 1974 June 23 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Soviet Jewry: Tribute to Soviet Jewish Art and Culture, 1974 June 23 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Soviet Jewry: Prisoner of Conscience Family Visits, 1974 July 11-12 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Soviet Jewry: Anniversary of "The Night of the Murdered Poets,", 1974 August 12 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Soviet Jewry: New Years Greeting Card Project for Soviet Jews and Synagogues, 1974 September (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Soviet Jewry: Panov Debut in Philadelphia, 1974 December 10 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Soviet Jewry: Unity Day with Soviet Jews on Simhat Torah, 1974 October 07-09 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Soviet Jewry: National Conference on Soviet Jewry Plenum, 1974 October 14 (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - Soviet Jewry: Dentist's Vigil for Soviet Jewish Dentists, 1974 November 08 (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Soviet Jewry: Women's Plea for Soviet Jewry, 1974 November 25 (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - Soviet Jewry: Women's Plea for Soviet Jewry, 1974 November 25 (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - Soviet Jewry: Women's Plea for Soviet Jewry - "Voices of Soviet Jewish Women,", 1974 (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - Soviet Jewry: First International Seminar on Soviet Jewry (Kiryat, Anavin, Israel), 1974 December 22-28 (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - Soviet Jewry Vigil, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - Soviet Jewry: Prisoner of Conscience and Refusenik Lists, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 24)
  - Soviet Jewry: Adopt a Prisoner Project, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 25)
  - Soviet Jewry: Refuseniks and Prisoners of Conscience, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 26)
  - Soviet Jewry: National Conference on Soviet Jewry (NCSJ), 1974 (Box 37, Folder 27)
  - Soviet Jewry: NCSJ News Release, 1974 (Box 37, Folder 28)
  - Soviet Jewry Newsletters - "JCCGW Yachad-Solidarity,", 1974 (Box 37, Folder 29)
  - Soviet Jewry: Appeal on behalf of Mikhail Shtern, 1975 January-December (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Soviet Jewry: Jackson Legislation on East-West Trade and Freedom of Emigration, 1975 January (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Soviet Jewry: Appeal on behalf of Mark Nashpits and Boris Tsitlionik, 1975 March-June (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Soviet Jewry: Communications Workers of America (CWA) Protest, 1975 April 11 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Soviet Jewry: Matzah of Hope Project, 1975 April (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Soviet Jewry: Solidarity Action with Moscow Hunger Strikes, 1975 April (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Soviet Jewry: Solidarity Day, 1975 April 13 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Soviet Jewry: Solidarity Day, 1975 April 13 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Soviet Jewry: Action Seminar on Soviet Jewry, 1975 April 27 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Soviet Jewry: Alexander Voronel Visit, 1975 April 27-29 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Soviet Jewry: Aborted Soviet Jewry Prayer Vigil, 1975April 29 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Soviet Jewry: National Conference on Soviet Jewry Leadership Assembly, 1975 May 04-05 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Soviet Jewry: Congressman Gilbert Gude Letter on behalf of Soviet Jewry, 1975 May (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Soviet Jewry: Bolshoi Ballet Demonstration, 1975 May 27 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Soviet Jewry: Kosharovsky-Karp Retraining Seminar, 1975 May-October (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Soviet Jewry: Anniversary of 1970 Leningrad Arrests, 1975 June 15 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Soviet Jewry: Bolshoi Opera Demonstration, 22 July-3 August 1975 Hermitage Art Exhibition Demonstration, 1975 July 30 (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Soviet Jewry: Memorial to the Murdered Poets, 1975 August (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Soviet Jewry: Appeal on behalf of Lev Roitburd and Anatoly Malkin, 1976 August (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - Soviet Jewry: New Year's Greeting Card Project, 1975 August-September (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - Soviet Jewry: Fenwick Commission on Helsinki Accord, 1975 September-December (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Soviet Jewry: Simhat Torah Unity Day for Soviet Jewry, 1975 September 27-28 (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - Soviet Jewry: World Peace Through Law Conference, 1975 October 12-17 (Box 38, Folder 23)
  - Soviet Jewry: World Peace Through Law Conference, 1975 October 12-17 (Box 38, Folder 24)
  - Soviet Jewry: Soviet Jewry Training Seminar with Alexander Goldfarb, 1975 October 23 (Box 38, Folder 25)
  - Soviet Jewry: Prisoner of Conscience Month/POC Demonstration, 1975 November 15 - December 15 (Box 38, Folder 26)
  - Soviet Jewry: List of Divided Soviet Jewish Families, 1975 (Box 38, Folder 27)
  - Soviet Jewry: Women's Plea for Soviet Jewry, 1975 December 10 (Box 38, Folder 28)
  - Soviet Jewry: Women's Plea for Soviet Jewry, 1975 December 10 (Box 38, Folder 29)
  - Soviet Jewry Vigil, 1975 (Box 38, Folder 30)
  - Soviet Jewry: Refusniks and Prisoners of Conscience, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Soviet Jewry: Adopt a Prisoner Project, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Soviet Jewry: Mail Delivery and Telephone Communication Problems with Refusniks, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Soviet Jewry: National Conference on Soviet Jewry (NCSJ), 1975 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Soviet Jewry: NCSJ News Release, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Soviet Jewry Newsletter - "Backgrounder,", 1975-1976 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Soviet Jewry Newsletters, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Soviet Jewry - Articles, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Soviet Jewry: Soviet Foreign Currency Gift Tax, 1976 January (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Soviet Jewry: Helsinki Declaration - Analyses, 1976 January-August (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Soviet Jewry: Second World Conference on Soviet Jewry (Brussels II), 1976 February 17-19 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Soviet Jewry: Second World Conference on Soviet Jewry (Brussels II), 1976 February 17-19 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Soviet Jewry: Second World Conference on Soviet Jewry (Brussels II), 1976 February 17-19 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Soviet Jewry: Second World Conference on Soviet Jewry (Brussels II), 1976 February 17-19 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Soviet Jewry: Appeal on behalf of Mark Dymshitz, 1976 February-March (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Soviet Jewry: Solidarity Day, 1976 April 04 (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Soviet Jewry: Solidarity Day, 1976 April 04 (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - Soviet Jewry: Mark Levitt Case/Soviet Propaganda, 1976 April 09 (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - Soviet Jewry: Matzah of Hope Project, 1976 (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - Soviet Jewry: Memorial Service for Colonel Yefim Davidovich, 1976 April 27 (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - Soviet Jewry: National Conference on Soviet Jewry Leadership Assembly, 1976 May 16-17 (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - Soviet Jewry: Aleksandr Luntz Visit, 1976 May 18 (Box 39, Folder 22)
  - Soviet Jewry: Memorial to the Murdered Poets, 1976 August 12 (Box 39, Folder 23)
  - Soviet Jewry: Appeal on behalf of Benor Gurfeil, 1976 August (Box 39, Folder 24)
  - Soviet Jewry: Appeal on behalf of Vladimir Slepak, 1976 August (Box 39, Folder 25)
  - Soviet Jewry: News Years Greeting Card Project, 1976 September (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Soviet Jewry: Babi Yar Memorial Observance, 1976 September 29 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Soviet Jewry: Easton, Pa. Christian Community Involvement in Soviet Jewry Movement, 1976 September-December (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Soviet Jewry: Simhat Torah Unity Day with Soviet Jewry, 1976 October 16-17 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Soviet Jewry: Beatings and Arrests of Moscow Jews, 1976 October (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Soviet Jewry: Soviet Jewry Seminar, 1976 October 28 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Soviet Jewry: Survey of Congregational Soviet Jewry Activities, 1976 November 04 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Soviet Jewry: Prisoner of Conscience Month/ Project POC, 1976 November 15 - December 15 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Soviet Jewry: 2nd National Interreligious Consultation on Soviet Jewry, 1976 November 30 - December 02 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Soviet Jewry: Women's Plea for Soviet Jewry, 1976 December 09 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Soviet Jewry: Moscow Conference on Jewish Culture/Parallel Symposia, 1976 December 21 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Soviet Jewry: Luther Place Memorial Church - Activities on Behalf of Soviet Jewry, 1976 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Soviet Jewry: Adopt A Prisoner Project, 1976 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Soviet Jewry: Prisoner of Conscience and Refunsenik Lists, 1976 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Soviet Jewry: Refunseniks and Prisoners of Conscience, 1976 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Soviet Jewry: Neshira/Soviet Jewish Emigration to Countries other than Israel, 1976 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Soviet Jewry: Mail Delivery Problems to Refusniks, 1976 (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Soviet Jewry Vigil, 1976 (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - Soviet Jewry: National Conference on Soviet Jewry (NCSJ), 1976 January-July (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - Soviet Jewry: National Conference on Soviet Jewry, 1976 August-December (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - Soviet Jewry: National Conference on Soviet Jewry News Release-Activities Report, 1976 (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - Soviet Jewry: Washington Committee for Soviet Jewry, 1976 (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - Soviet Jewry Newsletters, 1976 (Box 40, Folder 23)
  - Soviet Jewry: Solidarity Vigil, 1977 February 24 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Soviet Jewry: Soviet Ban on Importing Matzoh, 1977 February-March (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Soviet Jewry: Escalated Attacks on Refuseniks, 1977 March (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Soviet Jewry: Baltimore Conference on Soviet Jewry, 1977 March 27 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Soviet Jewry Rally, 1977 June 12 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Soviet Jewry Rally, 1977 June 12 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Soviet Jewry Rally, 1977 June 12 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Soviet Jewry: National Conference on Soviet Jewry Leadership Assembly, 1977 June 13-14 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Soviet Jewry: Memorial to the Murdered Poets, 1977 August 11 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Soviet Jewry: University of Maryland-Moscow University Exchange, 1977 September (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Soviet Jewry Unity Vigil for Gromyko Visit, 1977 September 23 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Soviet Jewry: Simhat Torah Unity Day with Soviet Jews, 1977 October 04-05 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Soviet Jewry Seminar, 1977 November 03 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Soviet Jewry Solidarity Week, 4-12 December 1977 Women Plea for Soviet Jewry, 1977 December 12 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Soviet Jewry: Visit of Alexander Slepak, 1977 December (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Soviet Jewry: Appeal on behalf of Anatoly Scharansky, 1977 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Soviet Jewry: Anti-Refusenik Propaganda Published in the USSR, 1977 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Soviet Jewry: Luther Place Memorial Church - Soviet Jewry Activities, 1977 (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - Soviet Jewry: Adopt a Prisoner Project, 1977 (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - Soviet Jewry: Refusenik and Prisoners of Conscience, 1977 (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - Soviet Jewish Emigration - Statistics and Procedures, 1977 (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - Soviet Jewry Vigil, 1977 (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - Soviet Jewry: National Conference for Soviet Jews (NCSJ), 1977 January-March (Box 41, Folder 23)
  - Soviet Jewry: NCSJ, 1977 April-August (Box 41, Folder 24)
  - Soviet Jewry: NCSJ, 1977 September-December (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Soviet Jewry: National Conference for Soviet Jews News Release, 1977 (Box 41, Folder 26)
  - Soviet Jewry: Washington Committee for Soviet Jewry, 1977 (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - Soviet Jewry Newsletter - "NCSJ Activities Report,", 1977 (Box 41, Folder 28)
  - Soviet Jewry Newsletter - "NCSJ News Bulletin,", 1977 (Box 41, Folder 29)
  - Soviet Jewry Newsletter - "Union of Council for Soviet Jews Alert,", 1977 (Box 41, Folder 30)
  - Soviet Jewry Newsletter - "Washington Committee for Soviet Jewry The Vigil,", 1977 (Box 41, Folder 31)
  - Soviet Jewry Newsletter - "Yachad/Solidarity,", 1977 (Box 41, Folder 32)
  - Soviet Jewry: Unidentified Photographs of Soviet Jewish Activists, 1977 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Soviet Jewry: Visit of Avital Scharansky and Alexander Slepak, 1978 January 25 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Soviet Jewry: Ash Wednesday Interfaith Human Rights Vigil, 1978 February 08 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Soviet Jewry: Solidarity Day Rally, 1978 April 09 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Soviet Jewry: Solidarity Day Rally, 1978 April 09 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Soviet Jewry: Visit of Vladimir Lazaris, 1978 April (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Soviet Jewry: Visit of Soviet Lawyers, 1978 April 18-23 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Soviet Jewry: Congressional Appeal on Behalf of Prisoner of Conscience Hillel Butman, 1978 May 11 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Soviet Jewry: Visit of Tzvi Essas, 1978 May (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Soviet Jewry: Visit of Dina Belina, 1978 June (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Soviet Jewry: Demonstration Against Soviet Show Trials and Harassment of Jews, 1978 June 14 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Soviet Jewry: B'nai B'rith International Soviet Jewry Strategy Session, 1978 August 01 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Soviet Jewry: Memorial to the Murdered Poets, 1978 August 13 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Soviet Jewry: Appeal of Glen Watts on Behalf of Slepak Family, 1978 August (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Soviet Jewry: Prisoner of Conscience Sukkah, 1978 October 15 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Soviet Jewry: Unity Day with Soviet Jews, 1978 October 24 (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Soviet Jewry: Soviet Jewry Regional Conference - Baltimore, 1978 October 29 (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - Soviet Jewry: Visit of Yanella Gudz, 1978 December 13-20 (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - Soviet Jewry: Human Rights Day Vigil, 1978 December 11 (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - Soviet Jewry: Appeal on behalf of Yosef Mendelevich, 1978 (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - Soviet Jewry: Appeal on behalf of Yuri Orlov, 1978 May-June (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - Soviet Jewry: Congressional Wives for Soviet Jewry, 1978 (Box 42, Folder 22)
  - Soviet Jewry: Adopt a Prisoner Project, 1978 (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - Soviet Jewry: Adopt a Prisoner Project - Prisoner of Conscience Lists, 1978 (Box 42, Folder 24)
  - Soviet Jewry: Refuseniks and Prisoners of Conscience, 1978 (Box 42, Folder 25)
  - Soviet Jewry: Efforts to Relocate the 1980 Moscow Olympics, 1978 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Soviet Jewry: Commodity Credit Corporation, 1978 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Soviet Jewry: "Zionism: Truth and Lies" - Translations From the Russian, 1978 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Soviet Jewry: Luther Place Memorial Church - Activities on behalf of Soviet Jewry, 1978 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Soviet Jewry: Soviet Jewry Vigil Leaflets, 1978 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Soviet Jewry: National Conference on Soviet Jewry (NCSJ), 1978 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Soviet Jewry: NCSJ News Releases, 1978 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Soviet Jewry: NCSJ Leadership Report, 1978 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Soviet Jewry: Washington Committee for Soviet Jewry, 1977 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Soviet Jewry Newsletter - "Alert,", 1978 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Soviet Jewry Newsletter - "The Vigil,", 1978 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Soviet Jewry Newsletter - "JCCGW Yachad/Solidarity,", 1978 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Soviet Jewry Newsletter - "Young Israel-Shomrai Emunah,", 1978 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Soviet Jewry Newsletter - "NCSJ News Bulletin,", 1978 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Soviet Jewry: Appeal on behalf of Anatoly Scharansky, 1979 March (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Soviet Jewry Freedom Bus, 1979 April 04-08 (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - Soviet Jewry: Early Release of Jewish Prisoners of Conscience, 1979 April (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - Soviet Jewry: Solidarity Day Rally, 1979 May 20 (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - Soviet Jewry: Solidarity Day Rally, 1979 May 20 (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Soviet Jewry: Solidarity Day Rally, 1979 May 20 (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - Soviet Jewry: National Conference on Soviet Jewry National Policy Conference, 1979 June 10-12 (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Soviet Jewry: Memorial to the Murdered Poets, 1979 August 02 (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - Soviet Jewry: Appeal on Behalf of Ida Nudel, Fall, 1979 (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - Soviet Jewry: Unity Day with Soviet Jews, 1979 October (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - Soviet Jewry Seminar, 1979 December 09 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Soviet Jewry Seminar, 1979 December 09 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Soviet Jewry: Luther Place Memorial Church Activities on behalf of Soviet Jewry, 1979 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Soviet Jewry Vigil, 1979 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Soviet Jewry Vigil, 1979 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Soviet Jewry: Prisoners of Conscience, 1979 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Soviet Jewry: Adopt a Prisoner Project, 1979 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Soviet Jewry Teaching Kit, 1979 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Soviet Jewry: National Conference on Soviet Jewry (NCSJ), 1979 January-May (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Soviet Jewry: NCSJ, 1979 June-December (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Soviet Jewry: NCSJ News Release, Activities Report, 1979 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Soviet Jewry: Washington Committee for Soviet Jewry, 1979 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Soviet Jewry: Miscellaneous Articles on Soviet Jews, 1979 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Soviet Jewry: Zionism and Israel as Presented in Soviet Books, 1979 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Soviet Jewry Newsletter - "Alert,", 1979 (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Soviet Jewry Newsletter - "The Vigil,", 1979 (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - Soviet Jewry Newsletters - "Young Israel Shomrai Emunah," "Jews in the USSR,", 1979 (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - Soviet Jewry Newsletters - "JCCGW Yachael/ Solidarity," "Backgrounder,", 1979 (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - Soviet Jewry Newsletter - "NCSJ News Bulletin,", 1979 (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - Soviet Jewry: Scharansky Birthday Vigil, 1980 January 20 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Soviet Jewry: Appeal on behalf of Ida Nudel, 1980 March-May (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Soviet Jewry: Nation Conference on Soviet Jewry Policy Conference, Washington D.C., 1980 April 13-15 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Soviet Jewry: Visit of Leib Knokh and Lev Ulanovrsky, 1980 April 16 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Soviet Jewry: Steinbruk, Brake, Silver Trip to Soviet Union, 1980 April 17-26 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Soviet Jewry: Steinbruk, Brake, Silver Trip to Soviet Union, 1980 April 26 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Soviet Jewry: Appeal on behalf of Adziashvili and Abassov, 1980 May-June (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Soviet Jewry: Memorial to the Murdered Poets, 1980 July 22 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Soviet Jewry: Let My People Go Rally At Lincoln Memorial, 1980 October 11 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Soviet Jewry: Let My People Go Rally At Lincoln Memorial, 1980 October 11 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Soviet Jewry Workshop, 1980 November 13 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Soviet Jewry: Human Rights Day Event (replacing Women's Plea), 1980 December 10 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Soviet Jewry: Luther Place Memorial Church Activities on behalf of Soviet Jewry, 1980 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Soviet Jewry: Refuseniks and Prisoners of Conscience, 1980 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Soviet Jewry: Adopt A Prisoner Project, 1980 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Soviet Jewry: National Conference on Soviet Jewry (NCSJ), 1980 (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - Soviet Jewry: NCSJ News Release, Press Service, Washington Wire, 1980 (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - Soviet Jewry Newsletter - "Alert,", 1980 (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - Soviet Jewry Newsletter - "The Record: The Jews of Russia,", 1980 (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - Soviet Jewry Newsletters - "Yacha/Solidarity," "Young Israel Shomrei Emunah,", 1980 (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - Soviet Jewry: Constituent Liaison Subcommittee, 1980-1981 (Box 45, Folder 21)
  - Israel and the Middle East Committee - Memos, Minutes, Correspondence, Reports, 1972 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Israel and the Middle East Committee - Memos, Minutes, Reports, 1973 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Israel and the Middle East Committee - Memos, Minutes, Reports, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Israel and the Middle East Committee - Memos, Minutes, Correspondence, Reports, 1975 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Israel and the Middle East Committee - Seminars Subcommittee, 1975 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Israel and the Middle East Committee - Memos, Minutes, Reports, 1976 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Israel and the Middle East Committee - Memos, Minutes, Reports, 1977 January-March (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Israel and the Middle East Committee - Memos, Minutes, Reports, 1977 April-December (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Israel and the Middle East Committee - Memos, Minutes, Reports, 1978 January-June (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Israel and the Middle East Committee - Memos, Minutes, Reports, 1978 July-December (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Israel and the Middle East Committee - Memos, Minutes, Reports, 1979 January-May (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Israel and the Middle East Committee - Memos, Minutes, Reports, 1979 June-December (Box 46, Folder 12)